wakeupnfuck.com 2019-07-27

# None

## Acceptance of this Privacy Policy

By using this Web site or any services provided at or through this web site, you expressly consent to the use and disclosure of information as described in this Privacy Policy. WAKEUPNFUCK.COM reserves the right to occasionally update this Privacy Policy without any prior notification to itself. However, we guarantee to post any changes made to this site. We strongly suggest you review our Privacy Policy every once in a while. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately after being posted on this Web site. In case you continue using WAKEUPNFUCK.COM Services or accepting our e-mails following the posting of changes to these terms, you will be considered to be fully aware of these changes and responsible for any breach of them. 

## Personal Information

WAKEUPNFUCK.COM allows you to visit the Web site without having to reveal any of your personal information. **_Your visit to this website is anonymous._** The personal information that you provide during the registration process will not be used for any commercial purposes and will not be sold, rented, leased or otherwise forwarded to any third party. We guarantee not to distribute or share your personal information provided it is not necessary to fulfill our obligations to you, and then only with the parties who adhere to WAKEUPNFUCK.COM's commitment to protecting your privacy and data. WAKEUPNFUCK.COM may provide your personal information if necessary, in WAKEUPNFUCK.COM’s good faith judgment, in case it is needed according to the existing law or in response to a valid subpoena, warrant, or order or in order to protect the rights of WAKEUPNFUCK.COM or others. 

## Email Newsletter and Opt-Out

At the moment you submit your e-mail address to WAKEUPNFUCK.COM, it will automatically be added to our E-Newsletter Subscriber List, which we use to send out news, notifications about current specials or updates that may be of interest to you. WAKEUPNFUCK.COM will not sell, rent, or lease your personal information to non-partner entities. You may also choose not to participate in the newsletter distribution. In case you don’t want to receive news messages from WAKEUPNFUCK.COM, you may terminate the subscription to our mailing program at any time. During the following database update your e-mail address will be removed from the E-Newsletter Subscriber List and no further mails will be sent to you. 

## Support

WAKEUPNFUCK.COM provides all users possessing valid subscriptions with e-mail support service. Unfortunately, at the moment WAKEUPNFUCK.COM does not provide telephone support. If you have any questions concerning about this Privacy Policy or our information handling practices, don’t hesitate to contact us via email. We promise to do our best to respond to your inquiry in as short time as possible.
